Hello friends welcome back video Q3 results
video will cover the
result of ICICI Lombard General Insurance
where BSC script code is 540716
and on NSC we know the company
by the name of ICICI so let's quickly
see the result from this article so I will
convert it into crores and tell you so first of all let's
talk about total income,
this quarter the communication was 4362
crores which was 4499 crores in the previous quarter
and 3856 crores in the same quarter of last year
so it is
seen here that the total income is there is a
slide decline on quarterly basis if we
talk about expenses then expenses of 400085 crores
in this quarter which was 3988 crores in the previous quarter
and
3531 crores in the
same quarter of last year so in this quarter
the company's profit was 317 crores so on
yearly basis here a good thing is seen, growth of
about 11% on quarterly
basis  There is a decline here. Now if we talk about the
9th monthly result, then here the
total income of 11493 crores has increased to
12839 crores and if we talk about profit, then the
profit has increased from 998 crores to
120092 crores. So here the revenue
is only a little big but the profit margin is very
big and with that the company has
beat the profit of last year.
In the three quarter results itself, one
quarter is still lying on the road, a good group can be
seen,
so 7.1 is coming out in front,
Rishu, if we look at it, it is above hundred.
If it is above hundred, then it
means that the claims and
expenses that the company is making are more than its earnings,
so this thing will turn out to be negative here
for the company. Let us take a look
at the chart, today a
slide ground was seen in ICICI Lombard, the stock
closed at 1249.30, at
1200 for quite some time now.  The stock is trading between 1275
and is
taking good support at 200M, so as long as it gets support here at 200M, the
stock will keep moving upwards,
if it breaks this 200M, then
we can see a sharp fall here,
after that the next support level will be 1125, if we
talk about the info, the range is from 1230 to 1255, the
low is ₹1000, the high in 52 weeks
is 1455, if we talk about the performance, then
here the revenue is seen to be good, the
profit bars are also good but the
profit margin seems to be improving in the recent days,
in the next video